<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Health Controller</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="text_welcome">Welcome to your Health Controller</string>
    <string name="sub_header_text">To control your health as a professional nutriant</string>
    <string name="bmi_string">\nBody Mass Index  \n\nYour BMI is an indirect measure of your body composition -- or how much body fat you have. Although BMI doesn’t measure body fat directly, it uses your weight and height to determine whether you’re classified as underweight, normal weight, overweight or obese. \nThis measurement correlates moderately well with other measurements of body fat such as skinfold measurements and underwater weighing, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.   \n\nBMI is measured by dividing your weight in pounds by the square of your height in inches, then multiplying by 703. The equation looks like this: \nBMI = (weight / height x height) x 703.  \nIf you\'re a woman who is 125 pounds and 5 feet 4 inches, \nyour BMI = (125 / 64 x 64) x 703 = 21.4. \nThis BMI puts you in the normal weight range.   \n\n1)A BMI below 18.5 indicates that you’re underweight.\n\n2) A BMI between 18.5 and 24.9 classifies you as a normal weight.\n\n3) A BMI between 25 and 29.9 puts you in the overweight category.\n\n4) A BMI of 30 or above classifies you as obese.</string>

    <string name="bmr_string">\nBasal Metabolic Rate\n\nYour BMR is the number of calories your body burns at rest to do basic functions like breathing, digesting, keeping your heart beating and all the other physiological tasks that keep you alive. \nYour BMR is partly determined by genetics, but other factors, like your body composition and activity level, may also have an effect on your BMR.\nThere are equations used to determine your BMR, and they differ based on whether you are a man or a woman. \n\nA woman can determine her BMR by plugging her stats into the Harris-Benedict equation \n= 655 + (4.35 x weight in pounds) + (4.7 x height in inches) – (4.7 x age in years). \n\nThe equation for a man to calculate his BMR is as follows \n= 66 + (6.23 x weight in pounds) + (12.7 x height in inches) – (6.8 x age in years).</string>


    <string-array name="food_name">
        <item>1 Cup Cow\'s Milk</item>
        <item>1 Cup Goat\'s Milk</item>
        <item>1 Cup Strawberry Milk</item>
        <item>1/2 Cup Vanilla Ice Cream</item>
        <item>1/2 Cup Apple Juice</item>
        <item>1/2 Cup Grape Juice</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="food_calorie">
        <item>157</item>
        <item>264</item>
        <item>244</item>
        <item>135</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>78</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
